Master Sergeant Origami Tobiichi, your suspension is lifted as of today.
Ma'am.
There will be no second chance. See that it doesn't happen again.
Captain, please stop!
Major Tsukamoto, would you care to explain this order?
Captain Kusakabe?
This calls for an independent unit from DEM Industries to the AST
and for them to be granted discretionary powers during emergency situations.
Forming a unit like this is absurd!
The AST might as well have been bought and paid for by those jerks at DEM!
I agree.
This area has had more spatial quakes in the last year than anywhere else.
Yet you've all been too busy playing house to capture even a single spirit.
That's why we're here.
Who are you?
We're the DEM soldiers assigned to the AST and I'm Jessica Bailey.
So nice to meet you.
The annual cultural festival is just another battle.
Performers fight it out on stage with their rivals.
Vendors compete with sales from their stalls.
And some wander the grounds by themselves, combating loveliness.
Vendors compete with sales from the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST.
Vendors compete with sales from the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST and the AST.
出逢い
繋がるストーリーで
この胸の鼓動を理解できないなら このまま落ちてゆくだけ さあ選んで 産むなデート 始めましょう
I'm going to talk to you, and I'm going to laugh.
I'm going to wake up with this dream.
I'm not going to give up.
I'm going to be like this,
I'm going to be like this.
And now the results of our nomination battle for self-preservation.
Rumored to work way hard even in soul-sucking sweatshop conditions,
our committee selection for this year's Tenno Festival is...
Shiro Itsuka!
Super glad it's not me.
Huh?
Nice. Couldn't ask for a better sacrificial lamb.
What's this Tenno Festival thingamabob?
It's the joint cultural festival held by the ten high schools here in Tengu City.
Those guys are already working my butt off and it's only the first day.
Sorry you had to come all the way out here to meet me.
It's okay. Toka was so hungry that she collapsed.
I had to go before she took a bite of me.
That's the spatial quake alarm. Kotari?
Acknowledged. Quick draw to the practice miss immediately.
We'll take you to the scene.
Let me sing you a song and let's sing along.
The greatest gift of all are all the stars up in the sky.
Millions sparkle above and shine.
That's D.Va?
Through the dark they light up in the light.
This spirit was first sighted six months ago and hasn't been seen since.
Basically we have zero information about her or her abilities.
I advise you to exercise caution when approaching her.
The greatest gift of all are all...
Who's there?
Oh great! Nice job, idiot!
Sorry! I can barely see where I'm going!
Hello? Do I have an audience out there?
I can't see you wherever you are.
If it's not inconvenient would you care to talk for a while?
Kotari!
Right. Move in closer.
We'll help you out with what to say.
Okay, the choices just popped up.
Selections, everyone!
You climbed all the way up here just to see me?
Lovely night, isn't it?
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, hello there, miss!
Huh?
I didn't mean to eavesdrop on you singing, but your voice is beautiful.
Happiness level, mood, mental state, all parameters are plummeting fast, Commander.
Guess that was the wrong choice.
We have to keep trying. Let's go with number one!
Has anyone ever told you how gorgeous you are?
I mean, wow!
Happiness levels are dropping further.
It's almost as if she's disgusted by Shido.
Damn it!
Looks like number three is our last resort.
The view from below was very...
Now she thinks he's lower than a cockroach!
But he didn't even get to finish the line!
You okay?
Are you okay?
Well, this is rather unexpected.
Why haven't you fallen down yet?
Why aren't you dead?
Disappear from this stage, this world, and this confluence of time and space!
Do it as soon as possible, you wretched plebeian!
Hold up! You serious?!
I said disappear, not talk!
I'd rather you not even expend the energy unleashing your halitosis-laden breath!
Are you too stupid to realize that your mere presence contaminates the purity of the air?
Okay, that's rude.
You're not very good at following instructions, are you?
Can you even begin to comprehend why I wouldn't stomp on your hands right now and send you falling to your death?
Because I care about the bottom of my shoe too much to let it touch filthy scum like you!
The AST!
Oh, wow! Cool!
Their armor is Trey Chic!
Talk about perfect! It's just the audience I was looking for!
You in particular!
Yeah!
More!
It's exciting as you!
You're having so much fun!
Would you like me to sing for you?
Fine!
But you could have just said no!
Once again, they're too busy playing to get anything done.
I guess I'll have to step in!
That kid!
Shino!
There! I found him!
That's enough for now! Bring him back!
Ah!
Why do I have to be here on a Saturday?
We have to practice for the talent show, so we'll leave the joint meeting in your capable hands!
And don't worry, we've arranged escorts!
Back off already! You're smothering the poor guy!
I was about to say the same thing!
Hello everyone!
Thank you for coming to the meeting! Let's get started!
What? No way!
One of my contacts brought this hidden camera footage from one of her secret concerts!
Miku is a yoi, huh?
I never would have guessed that she was a spirit!
Well, she's the one I saw! Hold on, do you know her?
No, but I've heard of her before!
She's done some songs for commercials and TV shows and shows and shows that she's
the same thing!
Oh!
Oh, Oh!
If I was trying to hear her before, she's done some songs for commercials and TV shows
and stuff!
She debuted six months ago, already has several hits, and her voice has been described as audio
ecstasy!
But she still remains anonymous, a mysterious idol who has never revealed herself to the public!
The fact that she's stayed off our radar for this long means she's good at hiding
out!
Hold on!
There's that other spirit like you.
For convenience, we've given her the code name Phantom!
According to the internet, Miku has an extreme distaste for men.
men. Only girls were allowed into this concert. And that's not all. Rumor has it, at some of her
prior events, she even took some female fans home. Whoa, what are you saying? It's entirely possible
that Little Miss Popstar Spirit prefers to swing the other way. If that's true, I won't be able to
do anything about her, will I? Best assured, we have a plan. Best of luck. You'll need it, sis.
Remember, you'll have to contact Miku while everyone is busy setting up, understand?
Do you really think this plan is going to work? Sure, if Raina's hypothesis is correct. But
don't worry your pretty little head, the entire crew has given your charm their stamp of approval.
Be confident, you'll be fine. How'd I get worked into this crap?
Voice changer. Yeah.
Okay, ready. Let's go.
So, um, that Shiro guy said there was something important that he had to go take care of.
And so he asked me if I would mind going to Tengu Square with everybody in his place.
That bastard. Like, what a loser.
That is so lame.
By the way, who are you?
Oh, right. Hello there. I'm Shiro's first cousin. My name's Shidomi? No scratch that. I'm Shiori.
Shiro, what are you up to?
I'm on a mission. Can you pretend like you don't know me?
Sure. You can always count on me. Nice to meet you, girl who's not Shiro in disguise.
Look over here. That's nice, Shiori. Very good. Now take something off.
No! What are you doing that for?
Don't worry. I'll still respect you.
Stop! Hold on!
No!
Rintoji's booths are in the first building.
There she is. I'm following her now.
Perfect. It's now or never.
Right.
Well, hello.
So what's your name?
Uh, I forgot.
You forgot?
I freeze up when I get nervous!
There's no need for you to be nervous around me.
But it's also irresistibly cute.
Happiness and mood levels haven't dropped yet.
They're actually staying stable.
I guess she prefers her woman dumb as a doorknob and helpless as a kitten.
Should be easy for Shido.
We have our choices! Make your selection!
Number two makes sense, but why is number three so popular?
Sounds perverted coming from a man, but it might be just a thing for the quirky Shiori to say.
Hmm. It would help us determine Miku's tolerance level.
Are you serious?
Try saying it like it's a joke.
I wonder...
What's up?
Would you be willing to sell me the panties you're wearing for 30,000 yen?
I have a counter bid. I don't want to sell them to you, but I'd consider trading them for the ones you're wearing.
Whoa, what?
I was just joking with you. Besides, shouldn't I be the one freaked by that question?
Totally! I was joking around, too.
Your uniform. You go to Ryzen, don't you?
Yeah, that's right.
Well then let's try this again. I'm Miku Izayoi and I go to Rindoji.
Right on. It's nice to meet you. My name's Shiori Itsuka.
That's a very pretty name.
The numbers are looking good. You should try asking her some questions.
So, uh, I thought this place was supposed to be off limits. What were you doing in here by yourself, Miku?
I love the stage. I have a hard time keeping away.
You love the stage?
Yes. I love feeling like everyone needs to hear my voice. When I sing, I can almost feel the excitement crackling through the air.
But not from you, which leads me to believe that you may never have heard of me.
Oh, well, I...
I seem to have put you on the spot. Don't worry about it. I won't tell that we were in here if you don't tell.
Well, it will be our little secret.
Uh, uh-huh.
Hmm. Now, let's get back to work, okay?
Okay.
Are you all right?
Oh, thank you.
You're quite welcome.
Come on, bro. Are the hamburgers ready yet?
Almost. Go ahead and set the table for me, would you?
It's so relaxing to just cook and not pretend to be my name.
You say that like you've already forgotten how liberating it feels to wear a skirt.
You're being ridiculous.
Never mind.
Fortunately, we have an excuse for you to meet up with Miku again.
Apparently, she likes to have tea with the girls she's taken a shining to once a week.
That's what we'll aim for next.
And now, Miku Izayoi will sing her hit, Mermaid Love Story.
She has such a lovely voice.
I want to do that, too!
You want to go do karaoke?
No, I want to do what she's doing!
What? You mean the drums?
Ba-dum!
They're here.
Is there something we can help you with?
Uh, yes, please.
I met Miku in Tengu Square yesterday.
What, are you another fan?
Not exactly.
That's what they all say.
I'm sorry, but this is supposed to be her private...
Hello again, Shiori.
Yo, what's up?
Ha-ha.
I wanted to say thanks.
You really shouldn't have gone to all this trouble.
No trouble at all.
I just had a very delicious tea blend delivered.
And it was so sweet of you to come all the way out here to my school just to return my handkerchief.
I had to share a cup with you.
This was supposed to be for those girls earlier, wasn't it?
Feels wrong to take their place.
Please, don't worry about them.
They're very obedient girls who always do what they've been told.
Ha-ha.
Wow, this is really good.
Everything's going smoothly.
We might be able to get her faster than we anticipated.
You know, you really are amazing.
I've never had anyone like you before.
Huh?
Shiori, don't you feel like there's something special between us?
I think that you should become a student at Rindouji.
What?
Now, don't you worry your pretty head one little bit about your grades or the cost.
I will personally request that you be passed through.
Hang on a second.
It's kind of sudden to decide on something like that.
Please, please, sir.
I... the answer is still no.
Hey, Shiori?
What can I do for you?
Please take up all your clothes.
Hey, I think you're great, but I can't do that.
I'm confused.
Why aren't you doing what I tell you?
So what does that mean, then?
Are you a spirit as well?
There's no point in trying to hide it anymore.
After all, there's no way an ordinary person could disregard a direct order from me.
And so I wonder, what in the world are you?
Are you a spirit?
Or worse, are you working for those wizards who have been trying to track me down and take me out?
I am...
What should we do?
If we try to cover it up, it'll make things worse.
It's gonna be risky, but we should try negotiating with her.
Look, I'm not a spirit.
I'm not a wizard either.
Just human.
That is so unfortunate.
Lying doesn't become you.
But I do have an ability that seals spirit powers away.
What is that supposed to mean?
Just what it sounds like.
So far, I've successfully sealed the power of five spirits.
As long as your powers are completely sealed, the AST won't be able to find you.
Trust me, there's a way you can live peacefully in our world.
I give you my word you won't have to be alone anymore.
Miku, trust me.
I just want to help you.
You know something?
I believe you.
Seriously?
But I don't need you to seal my powers for me.
Hmm?
The way things are right now, I don't think I could be much happier.
I have my powers and a life of luxury.
What more could I possibly need?
Just keep on pushing.
You have to convince her.
Look, Miku, you caused a major spatial quake in front of the train station a few days ago.
But why?
I'm not sure you have total control of your powers like you think you do.
Oh, so you know about that nasty incident?
Your concern is touching, but honestly, you don't need to worry about me.
I've got absolute control over my powers.
The spatial quake I caused the other day was not by accident, sweetie.
What could I do?
I'd never gotten a chance to sing at Tingo Arena before.
So naturally, when I passed it in front of the station, I suddenly felt the urge to sing.
Then I decided to let it go.
That's the reason you did it?
Yeah, I just couldn't help myself.
The desire to make music completely took me over.
If your friends had been there, they could have died.
Did that thought even occur to you, Miku?
I suppose I would have been upset.
Really? You would?
Then again, all the girls totally adore me no matter what.
I'm sure they would be satisfied knowing they had died for me.
Because they totally adore you?
Shido, try to calm down.
Yes. I have legions of fans that love me with all their hearts.
They do whatever I ask, whenever I ask them to do it.
Then you might want to know. I hate you.
Why's that?
You're intolerably arrogant and prideful.
Even if everyone in the world chose to accept a spoiled brat like you, I'd still hate your guts.
And as much as they'd love you, I'd hate you more.
Hearing such harsh words from you, they make me want you even more.
I have a burning desire to tease you mercilessly.
Until you come to me, crying, your face streaked with tears.
And shout, I love you, Miku.
Dream on. I will never belong to you.
Oh?
Then why don't we play a little game?
If your school somehow manages to win first place at the festival, then...
I'll agree to let you seal my powers right then and there.
A tenu festival?
That's right. I'm already participating in the stage portion, so you should put together a performance too.
But... you've got a serious advantage.
Well, that's your opinion.
The way I see it, I'm already doing you a big favor by allowing you to compete.
Now, the other side of the coin.
If Rindoji wins, I will have you.
Oh, and I also want each one of the spirits that you already sealed.
Will you agree to my terms?
Or do you want to run away?
Is this some kind of joke?
No. We're quite serious about it.
And if you have any issues with that, then you can simply go wait outside.
Did you say human targets? Oh, hell no. What is this crap?
We're after spirits here. We don't hunt down people.
And not only that, the operation is in Tengu Square during the school festival.
You want to fight spirits in a place where you're guaranteed a crowd?
This is a part of the ceremony. A cordial greeting to our admired adversaries.
Wait, what are you saying? Hold on, Northe.
Make sure Origami Tobichi doesn't find out about any of this.
What?
That's also a direct order from the top.
If you have any concerns, feel free to tell them.
What on earth was that about?
Shido Itsuka? Where have I heard that name?
No. Wasn't he Origami's...?
That's a complete voyage
The story of the futurist
I am the plans that I have built on patents
Thank you.